{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Jiā",
      "answer": "家"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jǐ",
      "answer": "几"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kǒu",
      "answer": "口"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhàopiàn",
      "answer": "照片"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hé",
      "answer": "和"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gè",
      "answer": "个"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jiějiě",
      "answer": "姐姐"
    },
    {
      "question": "Liǎng",
      "answer": "两"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dìdì",
      "answer": "弟弟"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīgòng",
      "answer": "一共"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hái",
      "answer": "还"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mèimei",
      "answer": "妹妹"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xiǎo",
      "answer": "小"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gǒu",
      "answer": "狗"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dāngrán",
      "answer": "当然"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhāng",
      "answer": "张"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhēn",
      "answer": "真"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kě'ài",
      "answer": "可爱"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ài",
      "answer": "爱"
    },
    {
      "question": "Méi",
      "answer": "没"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nán",
      "answer": "男"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zuò",
      "answer": "做"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gōngzuò",
      "answer": "工作"
    }
  ]
}
